

Iulian Prodea

github.com/iulianpro

Gloucester, England, United Kingdom



linkedin.com/in/iulian-pro



iulian.prodea@outlook.com



https://iulian.pro



+44 7424 693338

Summary

Experienced in Sales, Executive, Team Management, problem solving, "Can Do" attitude, hardworking, 100% involved in professional activity, trully passionate about technology and computers.

I have always been noticed by the management of the companies where I worked. Each time I was promoted to senior positions and even to management positions. This can be easily verified by contacting the former colleagues mentioned below.

I have been and I am very determined to become an experienced software developer, I continue to learn new things day by day and I am convinced that I will be able to add value to the organization I will work for and I will be a winning investment for that company.

Experience



Waking Night Support Care Worker

Holmleigh Care Homes Ltd

Aug 2019 - Aug 2020 (1 year 1 month)

As a waking night support care worker I was responsible with:

- Assisting Service Users with Personal Care and domestic duties.
- Create opportunities for Service Users to develop establish and maintain personal relationships and social networks, which encourage greater participation and integration in their chosen communities.
- Monitoring progress and recording notes on daily record sheets.
- Other in-house activities

Recommendation: Mrs. Joanne Howells, Office/Recruitment Manager can be contacted at +44 1452 300025, joanneh@holmleigh-care.co.uk



Area Sales Manager

S.A.R. CITY INSURANCE S.A., Cluj-Napoca, Romania Oct 2015 - Aug 2019 (3 years 11 months)

I have coordinated the activity of eight branches, meaning a team over 25 employees. Main responsibilities and actions has been:

- Driving sales processes and employees teams from eight territorial branches from NW of Romania;
- Developing strategies for growing business relationships with the company's partners;

- Recruitment candidates for vacancies;
- Tracking and fulfilling targets goals;
- Monitoring activity of the competition;
- Implementing the working procedures and the applicable law in insurance field;

Achievements: Together with the sales teams, I managed to increase the company's client portfolio as well as sales volumes by 30% each year.

Recommendation: Mr. Daniel Petcu, Chief Information Officer can be contacted at +40 21 2310054

Branch Manager

S.A.R. CITY INSURANCE S.A., Bucharest Romania Oct 2013 - Sep 2015 (2 years)

In this position I was responsible for:

- Launching, developing and coordinating a new branch in Bucharest;
- Developing strategies for growing business relationships with the company's partners;
- Recruitment candidates for vacancies;
- Tracking and fulfilling targets goals;
- Monitoring activity of the competition;
- Implementing the working procedures and the applicable law in insurance field;

Achievements: I was noticed by the company's management as one of the most productive employees, as proof that the Country Sales Manager proposed me to take over the position of Branch Manager.

Recommendation: Mr. Stefan Dicu, Country Sales Manager (2008 - 2015) can be contacted at +40 722 251708

Insurance Consultant

S.A.R. CITY INSURANCE S.A., Bucharest Romania

Apr 2012 - Sep 2013 (1 year 6 months)

In this position I was responsible for:

- Meeting with customers, understanding their needs and proposing tailored insurance solutions;
- Contacting existing customers by phone and proposing new insurance policies;
- Providing advices and support on insurance issues;
- Prospecting the market and identifying new potential customers;
- Identification of cross-selling solutions in order to increase the volume of sales;

Achievements: I was noticed by the company's management as one of the most productive employees, as proof that the Country Sales Manager proposed me to take over the position of Branch Manager.

Recommendation: Mrs. Mihaela Tache, Branch Manager (2012 - 2015) can be contacted at +40 722 277976

Education

Ocode Institute

Level 5 Diploma , Full Stack Software Developer 2019 - 2020

The course provided by the Code Institute was segmented into four chapters:

User Centric Frontend Development:

- HTML Fundamentals;
- CSS Fundamentals;
- Bootstrap 4;
- GitHub;
- Git Version Control;
- VS Code IDE;
- Project: https://iulianpro.github.io/my-city/ (I have passed it with 82%).

Interactive Frontend Development:

- Javascript;
- jQuery;
- DOM Manipulation;
- · Google Maps APIs;
- Project: https://iulianpro.github.io/discover-transylvania/ (I have passed it with 89%).

Data Centric Development:

- Databases Fundamentals;
- Python Fundamentals;
- SQL and noSQL;
- MySQL;
- Manipulated data with Python;
- · Flask Framework;
- MongoDB;
- CRUD Operations;
- Project: https://iulianpro-shifts-manager.herokuapp.com/ (I have passed it with 72%).

Full Stack Frameworks With Django:

- · Django Framework;
- Stripe;
- Amazon Web Services (S3);
- Project: https://iulianpro-give-help.herokuapp.com/ (I have passed it with 76%)